Task-it

Task-it is a simple and easy to use reminder app that helps its user to:
-manage todo’s/tasks
-set a remainder for each task
-get notified when it’s time (notification comes as an alarm)

Features:
-Sign up and Sign in functionality
-Beautiful and minimalistic user interface
-Alarm tone
-swipe delete task
-display lists of completed tasks
-ability to upload image from device
And lots more

Installation
We assume you've installed android studio already, Unzip the file and open it in android studio, sync and run..
Note: you need a basic knowledge of java to understand this app’s source code

How To Use
-After installing successfully on android studio, run on a virtual device or a physical device.
-sign up at the signup page, after signing up successfully, navigate to the home page, click on the FAB(floating action button) “+” to create a new task.
-for ads, remember to go to google admob, register if you haven’t, change the admob unit ID from ours to yours and start using.
-to change the logo, navigate to the manifest.xml file, look for android:roundIcon under application and change it to yours.
Happy using
About ME
My name is Abundance Nkereuwem, an undergraduate student of Computer Science in china
I love programing, i have been coding constantly for two years and I love it, stay tuned for more projects.
Feel free to message on Instagram @dremo.dev
